Finding Aid for Topographic Quadrangle Maps, 1895-[ongoing].
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- 7.5 Minute, Scale 1:24,000
  - Dafter - Gaylord
    - Dansville 42084E3
      - Survey 1970; print 1970; reprint 1973, green overprint
      - Survey 1970; print 1970; reprint 1976; photorevised, green overprint
      - Survey 1970; print 1970; reprint 1989; photorevised, green overprint
    - Davisburg 42083G5
      - Survey 1942; print 1945
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1971
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1973; photorevised, green overprint
    - Davison 43083A5
      - Survey 1969; print 1969; reprint 1971
      - Survey 1969; print 1969; reprint 1975; photorevised, green overprint
    - Dayton Center 43085E8
      - Survey 1982; print 1985; reprint 1985, green overprint
    - De Tour Village 45083H8
      - Survey 1964; print 1964; reprint 1965, green overprint
    - Deadmans Hill 45084A8
      - Survey 1984; print 1986; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - Dearborn 42083C2
      - Survey 1952; print 1952; reprint 1954, green overprint
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1970
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1973; photorevised, green overprint
    - Decker 43083D1
      - Survey 1963; print 1963; reprint 1964, green overprint
    - Deckerville 43082E6
      - Survey 1963; print 1963; reprint 1964, green overprint
    - Deer Lake 47088C1
      - Survey 1948; print 1949
      - Survey 1948; print 1949; reprint 1975; photorevised, green overprint
    - Deerfield 41083H7
      - Survey 1972; print 1972; reprint 1975, green overprint
    - Delaware 47088D1
      - Survey 1948; print 1949
      - Survey 1948; print 1949; reprint 1953, green overprint, shaded relief edition
      - Survey 1948; print 1949; reprint 1975; photorevised, green overprint
    - Delton 42085D4 (Folder Delton-Diffin)
      - Survey 1947; print 1947; reprint 1955, green overprint
      - Survey 1961; print 1961; reprint 1972; photorevised
      - Survey 1961; print 1961; reprint 1962, green overprint
      - Survey 1961; print 1961; reprint 1985; photorevised, green overprint
    - Denton 42083C5
      - Survey 1940; print 1942, green overprint
      - Survey 1953; print 1953; reprint 1955, green overprint
      - Survey 1969; print 1969; reprint 1971
      - Survey 1969; print 1969; reprint 1973; photorevised, green overprint
      - Survey 1969; print 1969; reprint 1980; photorevised, green overprint
    - Detroit 42083C1
      - Survey 1938; print 1947
      - Survey 1952; print 1952; reprint 1954, green overprint
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1971
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1973; photorevised, green overprint
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1980; photorevised, green overprint
    - Detroit-Wayne Airport 42083B3
      [earlier edition titled Wayne County Airport, later editions titled Flat Rock NE]
      - Survey 1952; print 1952; reprint 1954, green overprint
    - Devils Corner 45086F5
      - Survey 1981; print 1985; reprint 1985, green overprint
    - Dexter 42083C8
      - Survey 1964; print 1964; reprint 1966, green overprint
      - Survey 1964; print 1964; reprint 1975; photorevised, green overprint
    - Diffin 46087B1
      - Survey 1982; print 1985; reprint 1985, green overprint
    - Dimondale 42084F6 (Folder Dimondale-East Dayton)
      - Survey 1965; print 1965; reprint 1967, green overprint
      - Survey 1965; print 1965; reprint 1973; photorevised, green overprint
    - Diorite 46087E7
      - Survey 1955; print 1955; reprint 1956, green overprint
    - Dollar Settlement 46084D6
      - Survey 1951; print 1951; reprint 1955, green overprint
      - Survey 1951; print 1951; reprint 1976; photorevised, green overprint
    - Dowagiac 41086H1
      - Survey 1977; print 1981; reprint 1982, green overprint
    - Driggs Lake 46086D2
      - Survey 1972; print 1972; reprint 1975, green overprint
    - Driggs Lake SE 46086C1
      - Survey 1972; print 1972; reprint 1975, green overprint
    - Drummond 46083A6
      - Survey 1964; print 1964; reprint 1965, green overprint
      - Survey 1964; print 1964; reprint 1976; photorevised, green overprint
      - Survey 1964; print 1964; reprint 1994; photorevised, green overprint
    - Drummond Lake 46088D4
      - Survey 1982; print 1985; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - Drummond SE 46083A5
      - Survey 1964; print 1964; reprint 1966, green overprint
      - Survey 1964; print 1964; reprint 1976; photorevised, green overprint
      - Survey 1964; print 1964; reprint 1994; photorevised, green overprint
    - Duck Lake 42084D7
      - Survey 1976; print 1980; reprint 1980, green overprint
    - Dundee 41083H6
      - Survey 1972; print 1972; reprint 1975, green overprint
    - Durand 42083H8
      - Survey 1969; print 1969; reprint 1971
      - Survey 1969; print 1969; reprint 1975; photorevised, green overprint
    - Eagle 42084G7
      - Survey 1975; print 1978; reprint 1979
    - Eagle Harbor 47088D2
      - Survey 1946; print 1948
      - Survey 1946; print 1948; reprint 1975; photorevised, green overprint
    - East Dayton 43083D3
      - Survey 1963; print 1963; reprint 1964, green overprint
    - East Lansing 42084F4 (Folder East Lansing-Epoufette)
      - Survey 1970; print 1970; reprint 1973, green overprint
    - East Tawas 44083C4
      - Survey 1988; print 1989; reprint 1989, green overprint
    - Easton 43084A1
      - Survey 1975; print 1975; reprint 1978, green overprint
    - Eaton Rapids 42084E6
      - Survey 1965; print 1965; reprint 1967, green overprint
      - Survey 1965; print 1965; reprint 1973; photorevised, green overprint
    - Eckerman 46085C1
      - Survey 1951; print 1951; reprint 1955, green overprint
      - Survey 1951; print 1951; reprint 1975; photorevised, green overprint
    - Edenville 43084G4
      - Survey 1969; print 1969; reprint 1972, green overprint
    - Edmore 43085D1
      - Survey 1964; print 1964; reprint 1965, green overprint
    - Edwards 44084B3
      - Survey 1969; print 1969; reprint 1971, green overprint
    - Edwardsburg 41086G1
      - Survey 1977; print 1981; reprint 1982, green overprint
    - Elba 43083A4
      - Survey 1963; print 1963; reprint 1964, green overprint
      - Survey 1963; print 1963; reprint 1980; photorevised, green overprint
    - Eldorado 44084E4
      - Survey 1963; print 1963; reprint 1964, green overprint
    - Elkton 43083G2
      - Survey 1970; print 1970; reprint 1973, green overprint
    - Ellington 43083E3
      - Survey 1963; print 1963; reprint 1964, green overprint
    - Elmira 45084A7
      - Survey 1984; print 1986; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - Emerson 46085E1
      - Survey 1951; print 1951; reprint 1955, green overprint
      - Survey 1951; print 1951; reprint 1975; photorevised, green overprint
    - Engadine 46085A5
      - Survey 1973; print 1973; reprint 1977, green overprint
    - Ensign 45086H7
      - Survey 1982; print 1985; reprint 1985, green overprint
    - Epoufette 46085A2
      - Survey 1964; print 1964; reprint 1966, green overprint
    - Erie 41083G4 (Folder Erie-Fennville)
      - Survey 1940; print 1943
      - Survey 1952; print 1952; reprint 1953, green overprint
      - Survey 1967; print 1967; reprint 1969
      - Survey 1967; print 1967; reprint 1979; photorevised
    - Escanaba 45087F1
      - Survey 1981; print 1985; reprint 1985, green overprint
    - Essexville 43083E7
      - Survey 1967; print 1967; reprint 1969
      - Survey 1967; print 1967; reprint 1973; photorevised, green overprint
    - Estey 43084G2
      - Survey 1969; print 1969; reprint 1972, green overprint
    - Estral Beach 41083H2
      - Survey 1940; print 1942
      - Survey 1952; print 1952; reprint 1953, green overprint
      - Survey 1967; print 1967; reprint 1969
    - Evans 43085B4
      - Survey 1972; print 1972; reprint 1974, green overprint
      - Survey 1972; print 1972; reprint 1982; photorevised, green overprint
    - Evans Creek 44083H6
      - Survey 1972; print 1972; reprint 1975, green overprint
    - Evart SW 43085G4
      - Survey 1976; print 1976; reprint 1979; orthophotoquad
    - Evergreen Shores 45084H6
      - Survey 1964; print 1964; reprint 1966, green overprint
    - Fairgrove 43083E5
      - Survey 1963; print 1963; reprint 1964, green overprint
      - Survey 1963; print 1963; reprint 1973; photorevised, green overprint
    - Fairport 45086E6
      - Survey 1981; print 1985; reprint 1985, green overprint
    - Fairview 44084F1
      - Survey 1972; print 1972; reprint 1975, green overprint
    - Fayette 41084F3
      - Survey 1960; print 1960; reprint 1971; photorevised, green overprint
      - Survey 1981; print 1985; reprint 1985, green overprint
    - Felch 45087H7
      - Survey 1983; print 1986; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - Feldtmann Lake 47089G2
      - Survey 1984; print 1985; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - Feldtmann Ridge 47089G1
      - Survey 1984; print 1985; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - Fennville 42086E1
      - Survey 1977; print 1981; reprint 1982, green overprint
    - Fenton 42083G6 (Folder Fenton-Ford River)
      - Survey 1969; print 1969; reprint 1971
      - Survey 1969; print 1969; reprint 1975; photorevised
      - Survey 1969; print 1969; reprint 1983; photorevised, green overprint
    - Ferry 43086E2
      - Survey 1982; print 1985; reprint 1985, green overprint
    - Fibre 46084B6
      - Survey 1953; print 1953; reprint 1955, green overprint
      - Survey 1953; print 1953; reprint 1976; photorevised, green overprint
    - Fife Lake 44085E3
      - Survey 1983; print 1985; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - Fish Point 43083F5
      - Survey 1963; print 1963; reprint 1964, green overprint
    - Flat Rock 42083A3
      - Survey 1940; print 1942
      - Survey 1952; print 1952; reprint 1953, green overprint
      - Survey 1967; print 1967; reprint 1969
      - Survey 1967; print 1967; reprint 1973; photorevised, green overprint
    - Flat Rock NE 42083B3
      [earlier editions titled Wayne County Airport and Detroit Wayne Airport]
      - Survey 1967; print 1967; reprint 1969
      - Survey 1967; print 1967; reprint 1973; photorevised, green overprint
      - Survey 1967; print 1967; reprint 1980; photorevised, green overprint
    - Fletcher 44084E8
      - Survey 1950; print 1950; reprint 1953, green overprint
      - Survey 1950; print 1950; reprint 1978; photorevised, green overprint
    - Flint North 43083A6
      - Survey 1969; print 1969; reprint 1971
      - Survey 1969; print 1969; reprint 1975; photorevised, green overprint
    - Flint South 42083H6
      - Survey 1969; print 1969; reprint 1971
      - Survey 1969; print 1969; reprint 1975; photorevised, green overprint
    - Florence East 45088H2
      [earlier edition titled Commonwealth]
      - Survey 1962; print 1962; reprint 1964, green overprint
    - Florence West 45088H3
      [earlier edtion titled Stager]
      - Survey 1962; print 1962; reprint 1964, green overprint
    - Floyd 43084E4
      - Survey 1973; print 1973; reprint 1976, green overprint
    - Floyd Lake 44083C6
      - Survey 1988; print 1989; reprint 1989, green overprint
    - Flushing 43083A7
      - Survey 1969; print 1969; reprint 1971, green overprint
      - Survey 1969; print 1969; reprint 1975; photorevised, green overprint
    - Foote Site Village 44083D4
      - Survey 1988; print 1989; reprint 1989, green overprint
    - Ford River 45087F2
      - Survey 1981; print 1985; reprint 1985, green overprint
    - Forest Lake 46086C7 (Folder Forest Lake-Gaylord)
      - Survey 1982; print 1985; reprint 1985, green overprint
    - Forestville 43082F5
      - Survey 1963; print 1963; reprint 1964, green overprint
    - Fort Wilkins 47087D7
      - Survey 1948; print 1949, green overprint
      - Survey 1948; print 1948; reprint 1975; photorevised, green overprint
    - Fortune Lakes 46088A4
      - Survey 1944; print 1944; reprint 1956, green overprint
    - Foster City 45087H6
      - Survey 1983; print 1986; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - Fowlerville 42084F1
      - Survey 1973; print 1973; reprint 1977, green overprint
    - Frankenmuth 43083C6
      - Survey 1963; print 1963; reprint 1964, green overprint
      - Survey 1963; print 1963; reprint 1973; photorevised, green overprint
    - Frederic 44084G7
      - Survey 1983; print 1985; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - Freesoil 44086A2
      - Survey 1985; print 1987; reprint 1988, green overprint
    - Fremont 43085D8
      - Survey 1981; print 1985; reprint 1985, green overprint
    - Frontier 41084G5
      - Survey 1959; print 1959; reprint 1960, green overprint
    - Gaastra 46088A5
      - Survey 1944; print 1944; reprint 1976, green overprint
    - Gagetown 43083F2
      - Survey 1963; print 1963; reprint 1964, green overprint
    - Galesburg 42085C4
      - Survey 1947; print 1947; reprint 1955, green overprint
      - Survey 1961; print 1961; reprint 1962, green overprint
      - Survey 1961; print 1961; reprint 1972; photorevised, green overprint
      - Survey 1961; print 1961; reprint 1985; photorevised, green overprint
      - Survey 1975; print 1975; orthophotoquad
    - Galien 41086G4
      - Survey 1971; print 1971; reprint 1973, green overprint
    - Garden 45086G5
      - Survey 1981; print 1985; reprint 1985, green overprint
    - Garden Corners 45086H5
      - Survey 1982; print 1985; reprint 1985, green overprint
    - Garden Island West 45085G5
      - Survey 1976; print 1980; reprint 1981, green overprint
    - Garnet 46085B3
      - Survey 1973; print 1973; reprint 1977, green overprint
    - Gay 47088B2
      - Survey 1954; print 1954; reprint 1955, green overprint
      - Survey 1954; print 1954; reprint 1975; photorevised, green overprint
    - Gaylord 45084A6
      - Survey 1984; print 1986; reprint 1986, green overprint
  - Germfask - Long Lake West
    - Germfask 46085B8 (Folder Germfask-Grand Haven)
      - Survey 1972; print 1972; reprint 1975, green overprint
    - Gibbs City 46088B6
      - Survey 1945; print 1945; reprint 1956, green overprint
      - Survey 1945; print 1945; reprint 1975; photorevised, green overprint
    - Gilchrist 46085B4
      - Survey 1973; print 1973; reprint 1977, green overprint
    - Gilford 43083D5
      - Survey 1963; print 1963; reprint 1964, green overprint
      - Survey 1963; print 1963; reprint 1973; photorevised, green overprint
    - Gilletts Lake 42084C3
      - Survey 1970; print 1970; reprint 1973, green overprint
      - Survey 1970; print 1970; reprint 1976; photorevised, green overprint
    - Gimlet Creek 46085D3
      - Survey 1973; print 1973; reprint 1977, green overprint
    - Gladstone 45087G1
      - Survey 1981; print 1985; reprint 1985, green overprint
    - Gladwin 43084H4
      - Survey 1969; print 1969; reprint 1971, green overprint
    - Glenn 42086E2
      - Survey 1977; print 1981; reprint 1982, green overprint
    - Glennie 44083E6
      - Survey 1988; print 1989; reprint 1989, green overprint
    - Glovers Corner 46088H1
      - Survey 1982; print 1984; reprint 1984, green overprint
    - Gobles East 42085C7
      - Survey 1978; print 1981; reprint 1982, green overprint
    - Goetzville 46084A1
      - Survey 1964; print 1964; reprint 1966, green overprint
    - Golden Lake 46088B8
      - Survey 1978; print 1981; reprint 1982, green overprint
    - Goodar 44083E8
      - Survey 1972; print 1972; reprint 1975, green overprint
    - Goodells 42082H6
      - Survey 1937; print 1939
      - Survey 1952; print 1952; reprint 1954, green overprint
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1970, green overprint
      - Survey 1988; print 1991; reprint 1991, green overprint
    - Goodrich 42083H5
      - Survey 1969; print 1969; reprint 1971
      - Survey 1969; print 1969; reprint 1975; photorevised, green overprint
    - Goose Island 45084H4
      - Survey 1964; print 1964; reprint 1966, green overprint
      - Survey 1964; print 1964; reprint 1975; photorevised, green overprint
    - Gooseneck Lake 46086A5
      - Survey 1982; print 1985; reprint 1985, green overprint
    - Gordonville 43084E3
      - Survey 1973; print 1973; reprint 1976, green overprint
    - Gould City 46085A6
      - Survey 1973; print 1973; reprint 1977, green overprint
    - Gourley 45087E4
      - Survey 1988; print 1989; reprint 1989, green overprint
    - Government Peak 46089G6
      - Survey 1977; print 1981; reprint 1981, green overprint
    - Grand Haven 43086A2
      - Survey 1972; print 1972; reprint 1975, green overprint
      - Survey 1972; print 1972; reprint 1980; photorevised, green overprint
    - Grand Marais 46085F8 (Folder Grand Marais-Gull Island)
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1970, green overprint
    - Grand Marais NE 46085F7
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1970, green overprint
    - Grand Marais SE 46085E7
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1970, green overprint
    - Grand Rapids East 42085H5
      - Survey 1967; print 1967; reprint 1969
      - Survey 1967; print 1967; reprint 1972; photorevised, green overprint
    - Grand Rapids West 42085H6
      - Survey 1967; print 1967; reprint 1969
      - Survey 1967; print 1967; reprint 1972; photorevised, green overprint
    - Grand Sable Lake 46086F1
      - Survey 1966; print 1966; reprint 1968, green overprint
    - Grandville 42085H7
      - Survey 1958; print 1958; reprint 1960, green overprint
      - Survey 1958; print 1958; reprint 1972; photorevised, green overprint
    - Granite Point 46087G5
      - Survey 1982; print 1985; reprint 1985, green overprint
    - Grant 43085C7
      - Survey 1981; print 1985; reprint 1985, green overprint
    - Grass Lake 42084C2
      - Survey 1973; print 1973; reprint 1989, green overprint
    - Graveraet River 47088A7
      - Survey 1954; print 1954; reprint 1956, green overprint
    - Graveraet River 47088A7
      - Survey 1954; print 1954; reprint 1975; photorevised, green overprint
    - Grayling 44084F6
      - Survey 1950; print 1951
      - Survey 1950; print 1950; reprint 1989, green overprint
    - Green Hills 46087C6
      - Survey 1983; print 1986; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - Green Timbers 45084B5
      - Survey 1984; print 1986; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - Greenbush 44083E3
      - Survey 1988; print 1989; reprint 1989, green overprint
    - Greenville East 43085B2
      - Survey 1972; print 1972; reprint 1974, green overprint
    - Greenville West 43085B3
      - Survey 1972; print 1972; reprint 1974, green overprint
    - Greenwood 46087D7
      - Survey 1955; print 1955; reprint 1956, green overprint
      - Survey 1955; print 1955; reprint 1975; photorevised, green overprint
    - Gregory 42084D1
      - Survey 1973; print 1973; reprint 1977, green overprint
    - Grosse Pointe 42082D8
      - Survey 1952; print 1952; reprint 1953, green overprint
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1971
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1973; photorevised, green overprint
    - Gull Island 45085F7
      - Survey 1984; print 1986; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - Gulliver 45086H1 (Folder Gulliver-Hesperia)
      - Survey 1972; print 1972; reprint 1975, green overprint
    - Gwinn 46087C4
      - Survey 1952; print 1952; reprint 1954, green overprint
      - Survey 1952; print 1952; reprint 1975; photorevised, green overprint
    - Hadley 42083H4
      - Survey 1943; print 1945
      - Survey 1943; print 1945, green overprint
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1970, green overprint
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1978; photorevised, green overprint
      - Survey 1988; print 1991; reprint 1991, green overprint
    - Hale 44083D7
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1971, green overprint
    - Hale SE 44083C7
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1971, green overprint
    - Hamburg 42083D7
      - Survey 1965; print 1965; reprint 1967, green overprint
      - Survey 1965; print 1965; reprint 1975; photorevised, green overprint
      - Survey 1965; print 1965; reprint 1983; photorevised, green overprint
    - Hamilton West 42086F1
      - Survey 1978; print 1981; reprint 1982, green overprint
    - Hancock 47088B5
      - Survey 1946; print 1948
      - Survey 1946; print 1946; reprint 1975; photorevised, green overprint
    - Hangore Heights 45084D3
      - Survey 1982; print 1986; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - Harbor Beach 43082G6
      - Survey 1970; print 1970; reprint 1973, green overprint
    - Hardwood Island 46085C7
      - Survey 1972; print 1972; reprint 1975, green overprint
    - Hardwood Lake 45084B4
      - Survey 1984; print 1986; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - Harlan 44085D7
      - Survey 1985; print 1987; reprint 1988, green overprint
    - Harrietta 44085C6
      - Survey 1985; print 1987; reprint 1988, green overprint
    - Harrisville 44083F3
      - Survey 1988; print 1989; reprint 1989, green overprint
    - Hartland 42083F7
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1971
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1975; photorevised, green overprint
    - Harvey 46087D3
      - Survey 1982; print 1985; reprint 1985, green overprint
    - Hawks 45083C8
      - Survey 1971; print 1971; reprint 1974, green overprint
    - Helena 46087B3
      - Survey 1988; print 1989; reprint 1989, green overprint
    - Helps 45087H5
      - Survey 1983; print 1986; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - Hemlock 43084D2
      - Survey 1975; print 1975; reprint 1978, green overprint
    - Henderson Lakes 45087E2
      - Survey 1981; print 1985; reprint 1985, green overprint
    - Hermansville 45087F5
      - Survey 1988; print 1989; reprint 1989, green overprint
    - Hesperia 43086E1
      - Survey 1982; print 1985; reprint 1985, green overprint
    - Hessel 46084A4 (Folder Hessell-Howell)
      - Survey 1964; print 1964; reprint 1966, green overprint
    - Hetherton 45084A3
      - Survey 1984; print 1986; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - High Island 45085F6
      - Survey 1984; print 1986; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - Highland 42083F5
      - Survey 1942; print 1945, green overprint
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1971, green overprint
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1973; photorevised, green overprint
    - Highland Park 42083D1
      - Survey 1952; print 1952; reprint 1954, green overprint
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1971
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1973; photorevised, green overprint
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1983; photorevised, green overprint
    - Hillman 45083A8
      - Survey 1984; print 1986; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - Hillman NE 45083B7
      - Survey 1984; print 1986; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - Hillsdale 41084H6
      - Survey 1959; print 1959; reprint 1960, green overprint
    - Hog Island East 45085G3
      - Survey 1984; print 1986; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - Hog Island Point 46085A3
      - Survey 1973; print 1973; reprint 1977, green overprint
    - Hog Island West 45085G4
      - Survey 1984; print 1986; reprint 1986, green overprint
    - Holland East 42086G1
      - Survey 1972; print 1972; reprint 1975
      - Survey 1972; print 1972; reprint 1975, green overprint
      - Survey 1972; print 1972; reprint 1980; photorevised, green overprint
    - Holland West 42086G2
      - Survey 1972; print 1972; reprint 1975
    - Holton 43086D1
      - Survey 1981; print 1985; reprint 1985, green overprint
    - Hope 43084G3
      - Survey 1969; print 1969; reprint 1972, green overprint
    - Howard City 43085D4
      - Survey 1981; print 1985; reprint 1985, green overprint
    - Howe Lake 46087H8
      - Survey 1982; print 1984; reprint 1984, green overprint
    - Howell 42083E8
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1970
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1975; photorevised, green overprint
      - Survey 1968; print 1968; reprint 1983; photorevised, green overprint